[{"answer": "No, actually, we haven't.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "I don't think you two have ever been together for a primetime interview, have you?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Eight years.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "How long have you been together?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, I feel like anyone who is sort of engaging themselves in tabloid press as fact will -- you know you'll always have the last laugh.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Do you know -- do you feel like you're having the last laugh for all those who mocked it?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, one, I think you have to make your relationship a priority.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How do you make it work?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I would say so.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Is he -- is he romantic?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "No, he's very --", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Or is he ruggedly you know?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I think he's a little bit -- I think he's a little bit of both.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Tucked you over his shoulder and wheel you home for dinner?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Wow, my favorite.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What's your favorite Post-It note?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "You are a little old softie, aren't you?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Are you happy with how he's gone on?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "When you first got into this, did you ever imagine it would become a primary new source in that way?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "The rules -- the phone goes down at dinner.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What are the rules?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "It is slightly perverse.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "But isn't it slightly perverse?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, the average age of entry into the sex trade is 13 years old, and that's globally.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "How big of a factor was it that you've got three young girls yourself and you could look at them and perhaps see them transplanted into this hideous world?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, I think that there's -- I think that there's a subsect of what we're looking at it and it's sort of dangerously bleeds over into something that people are very accustomed to.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Why was that, do you think?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Prostitution?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "That's why we're using social media for this campaign, is to actually go right into the heart of where it's taking place.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What do you think about that conundrum?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "He lied to me about his age.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "And so was he deceitful in the kind of person that he described himself as?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "No, what she's describing is -- I mean the stories do start to take on a very similar kind of framework with the pimp.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "I mean is this a familiar story of how these things start?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, at first he told me, you know, I'll take you shopping and I will give you anything that you want and I'll take you out of the life that you're in.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "And what did he put you through?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "At first it was just him, and then when I had escaped to get home, I had to call somebody.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What was going on?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I was around 14, 15.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "And how old were you then?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I would tell them to go to an adult that is trustworthy, and that would listen to them, and that they're worthwhile waiting on, and they have a lot of people that do care about them, and that is there for them.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Finally, what would you say to other girls who find themselves in the same kind of situation?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "And then the abuse continues.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "You know, this a multi-faceted form of abuse, isn't it?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "How do those girls without the help of organizations like yourselves ever get out of that cycle?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Great question, Piers.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "How much money is the U.S. government spending on, say, policing drugs compared to sex slavery?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, first, look, the reason why we've initiated this campaign is we have to create awareness.", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "If you were in charge of policy in this area, what is the key thing that should be done?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Probably longer,", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "I mean, could you be in this for 30 years?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I just finished a movie called \"New Year's Eve.\"", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What are you up to now movie-wise?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes, I --", "docId": "110414pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Has that taken over in priorities for both of you?", "qSentId": 563}]